http://www.pctex.com/policy.html

ProductsSoftwarePricingUpgradesBooksFontsAdd-OnsDownloadsTrial VersionsVideosManualsUpdatesStore Online Store Product ListOrdering Options Shopping Cart CheckoutFind a resellerSupportOn TeX and LaTeXHelp Using PCTeXInstallationRegistrationHelp with FontsAsk for Support PCTeX ForumsAbout UsThe CompanyPrivacy PolicyContact Us
Home
PCTeX 6
MathTime Pro Fonts
Lucida Fonts
Table Manual
Videos
PCTeX tips
Free & Trial Versions
identify or contact a specific individual, such as a name,
address, telephone number or e-mail address. We collect
personal information in several ways from different parts of
our Web site.
How We Use Collected Information
We use your personal information to provide you with products
and services, to better understand your needs and interests,
and to facilitate your use of and purchases from our store.
If you request something from our web site (a product, a
product evaluation, or support services as examples), we will
use the information you provide to fulfill your request. For product and service purchases, contact
information is used to ship products to you, and financial
information is used to bill you for those products and
services.
We Do Not Share Your Information
We will not sell or rent your personal information to others.
Our Policy May Change
We may revise this privacy policy. This privacy policy was
last updated on November 1, 2005. If there are updates to the
terms of this privacy policy, we will post the revised policy
and update the revision date in this paragraph. Please review
this policy periodically to be apprised of any updates.
© 2009. All Rights Reserved - Personal TeX, Inc.
- Site last updated Thu, 07 Mar 2013 11:24:01 -0800
